http://www.womens-health.co.uk/privacy.asp

Privacy Policy
By using this site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the
Terms of Use and Disclaimer,
Womens-health.co.uk collects certain information about you that
you specifically and knowingly provide to us, such as your user name, email address,
name or mailing address. In addition, we may track how you use this Site and relate
it to the information you have provided to us. If you wish to be notified of the
use of such tracking software and/or disable such software, your browser may offer
this feature by means of its options or preferences menu.
The above-described information (Personally-Identifying Information)
may be used by Womens-health.co.uk to personalize and enhance your
use of this Site, including the marketing and promotion of certain products and
services that might be of interest to you. Your use of this Site is a consent to the
foregoing use of your Personally-Identifying Information by Womens-health.co.uk
Womens-health.co.uk also may share your
Personally-Identifying Information with select companies and
organizations for their own marketing and promotional use. While Womens-health.co.uk seeks to share Personally-Identifying Information with companies that
follow appropriate privacy policies, it does not bear any responsibility for the actions and
policies of such third parties. If you wish that we not share your
Personally-Identifying Information with third parties, you may "opt out" by emailing us with such request.
You should be aware that any Personally-Identifying Information,
such as your user name and email address, as well as any other information
that you post on a bulletin board, share in a "chat room," or otherwise
specifically and knowingly disclose by use of the Forums, may be directly
collected and used by third parties. Therefore, you may be subject
to unsolicited email as a result of your disclosure of such information.
You should have no expectation of privacy with respect to your communications
through the forums.
Your Privacy
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org.
We partner with third-party advertising companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. These companies may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information [not including your name, address, email address or telephone number] during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
Additional Information
The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web.
Google, as a third party vendor,
uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
Google's use of the DART cookie
enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites
and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use
of the DART cookie by visiting the Google
ad and content network privacy policy.
Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we're unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the Network Advertising Initiative, or NAI, which suggests the following language for data collection of non-personally identifying information:
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here
Login to comment
Log in or sign up
Username:
Password:
(0 Comments)
Login to add a comment
Post a comment
You must be logged in to comment.
About Us | Conditions of Use | Privacy Policy | Contact Us
© 2020 Womens-Health.co.uk.All rights reserved.
